resolveltd.co.uk 2008-06-22

# Resolve - Privacy Policy

Resolve Ltd (“Resolve”, “the Company”, “We”, “Us”, “Our”) is committed to protecting your privacy online and this is at the heart of our service.  We respect your privacy – our entire service depends on treating personal information in confidence and with sensitivity. 

Resolve will only record your personal data as set out in the policy and we will not give, rent, sell or trade any of Your identifiable personal information without your prior express permission.

What do we collect and use personal information for?

  * To provide you with information about job vacancies available through this site;
  * To provide you with recruitment services;
  * To send you information about some of our other recruitment opportunities;
  * To anticipate any problems with services supplied to you;
  * To carry out market research and marketing analysis

We may need to collect and process personal information about you (including but not restricted to your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number), along with details of your current and previous employment history, education and training.  This may include sensitive data relating to you, including medical details, criminal offences or proceedings and details of race and ethnic origin.  We may receive this information through this site or via one of our consultants.

Although we do not make it compulsory to give us every item of information we ask for, the more accurate information you volunteer, the better we can tailor our services for you.

We may occasionally contact you with information about some of our other recruitment opportunities that we feel may be of interest to you.  This will only come from us and only if you have not objected.

With whom is the information shared?

To the extent that it is necessary in connection with our business we will pass your data to our employees for the purpose of supplying recruitment services to you.

Only where we have gained your prior consent will we disclose or transfer your data to prospective employers.

We may analyse and disclose aggregate statistics about our site visitors and candidates in order to describe our services to prospective partners, clients and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

We may disclose personal information, if required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary, to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of the company, the site or its visitors.

The site contains links to other sites.  Resolve is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.

How will we use Your information?

Where we collect information from You for communication, we will use this to keep in touch with You as necessary to provide the Service.  We will not disclose your personal information to any other person without Your permission.

Transferring your personal information outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”)

As part of the services offered to you through our site, the information you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the EEA.  For example, this may happen if any of our servers are, from time to time, located in a country outside the EEA or where the prospective employers for a vacancy you are interested in is located in a country outside the EEA.  These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA.  If we transfer your information in this way we will takes steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

Security

Resolve places a great importance on the security of all personally identifiable information associated with our customers.  We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control.  While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.

E-Mail Communications

We do not rent out Your e-mail addresses to third parties for unsolicited e-mail communications.

Where you have given us your e-mail address we may occasionally send e-mail communications to you to provide information that we think you will find useful and interesting.  If you wish to unsubscribe and not receive future e-mail please send an e-mail to [enquiries@resolveltd.co.uk](mailto:enquiries@resolveltd.co.uk) with the word ‘unsubscribe’ as the heading.

Cookies

Cookies are not required to view our website, however to enable switching between text only and graphics versions of the site for the benefit of accessibility, cookies are used to recall your viewing preference.

Keeping our record accurate and up to date

Resolve regularly reviews the personal data it processes to ensure that it is up to date, accurate and not held for longer than necessary for our internal processes or as otherwise required by law.  Your co-operation in helping us to keep your data accurate by informing us of any change of name or address is an important part of this.  If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied to us you may do so at any time.

Security

Resolve uses encryption and authentication tools to protect your sensitive personal information.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Resolve and to our privacy policy.  If we change the privacy policy in any way, we will post these changes on this page.

Your rights

You have a legal right to a copy of all the personal information about you held by us.  You also have a right to correct any errors in that information.

Please e-mail any questions, comments you have about these policies, or requests not to receive details of future recruitment opportunities to [enquiries@resolveltd.co.uk](mailto:enquiries@resolveltd.co.uk); or write to

Resolve Ltd  
Oakhurst  
23 Harrogate Road,  
Chapel Allerton,  
Leeds LS7 3PD.
